It's been a while.
久しぶりだよな
I was in trouble for money.
お金困ってたよな
I bought Vance.
バンス買ってきたよな
What do you mean it's less than 20,000 yen?
2万円足らないからどういうことだよ
Na.
な
Because I don't have enough money.
お 金足りてないから
What?
なんて?
I wonder if I made it in time.
間に合えたか無理やねん
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
Did you do 2 cups?
2カップやったか?
picture?
え?
Good cup?
いいカップ?
Have you grown?
成長したの?
yes.
はい
What should I do?
どうしたらいいか?
Shall I call your mom?
お 母 さん電話しようか?
yes.
はい
Should I call your mom?
お 母さん電話する?
Oh, no.
あ、ダメです
Should I call your mom?
お母さん電話しようか?
Oh, I don't like it.
あ、嫌です
Would you like me to bring you 20,000 yen?
2万円持ってきてもらう?
Is there any other way?
何か他の方法がありますか?
What method is best?
どんな方法がいい?
Why are you stopping me?
なんで止めてやるの?
president.
社長
May I check your whole body?
全身チェックさせてもらおうかな
President, I think I'll buy it for 20,000 yen.
社長、俺が2万円で買っちゃおうかな
You can do whatever you want, right?
何してもいいでしょ?
Buy it for 20,000 yen.
2万円で買って
Anyone can see this.
誰も見えちゃうよ、これ
This 20,000 yen is cheap for the president.
これ2万円じゃ社長安いっすよ
Did you get a boyfriend?
彼氏できた?
I haven't been able to do it.
できてないです
It's no good if I make it, right?
作ったらダメだよね?
yes.
はい
Shall we try sunpee today?
今日サンピーしようか?
picture?
え?
Shall we sampy?
サンピーしようか?
She has a naughty face, something like this.
エッチな顔になってるよ、なんかこれ
I wanted to be eaten.
ご食されたかった
Yara
やら
do.
して
Amazing body.
す げえ体
It seems so naughty.
いやーやらしい
This is a joke, so let's take a look.
これがおしりぎしだから見てみようよ
As always.
いつもだとな
Because we can date this year.
今年付き合えるから
This is amazing.
すごいね、これ
Hey.
ね え
No, let's get some sunpee.
いや、もうサンピーしよう
I feel sorry for having to do something like this for 20,000 yen.
2万円でこんなことされて かわいそうだね
That's pretty awesome.
ちょちょ最高っすね
An unfortunate life.
残念な人生
sorry.
すみません
Show this photo to your mom.
お母さんにこの写真を見せて
please show me.
見せてください
what?
なん?
This is what will happen if you don't pay your money back.
お金返さないとこんなことになるんだよ
That's no good.
ダメだよね
Should I send it to my part-time job?
バイト先に送ろうか?
This video.
この動画
Please send it to me.
送 ってください
I can't work in a place like that for the rest of my life.
一生働けないで、そんなとこで
It looks like that.
あそこしいね
Yeah.
うん
This, this, this.
これこれこれだよ
Hey.
ね え
I don't know which one.
どっちかわかんないよ、そこ
Shall I keep messing with you?
ずっといじってあげようか?
Yeah.
うん
Do it for about 30 minutes.
30分くらいやって
That's no longer the case.
そんなんなくなってる
It's coming out a lot.
めっちゃ出てるじゃん
That's scary, Rico-chan.
やばいよ、リコちゃん
It's coming out a lot.
めっちゃ出てる
めちゃくちゃ出てる
When was the last time you had sex?
いつぶりエッチしたの?
half a year.
半年
About half a year?
半年くらい?
That's a lie.
それは嘘だよ
I just made it official.
ついこのままお正規したばっかりじゃん
It hasn't been half a year.
半年経ってないよ
It's only been about 2 months.
2ヶ月ぐらいしか経ってない
Isn't it more naughty than that?
それよりエッチしてないの?
Is that so?
そうなの?
what have you been up to?
何してたの?
Don't you have sex with your customers?
お客さんともエッチしてないの?
That's no good.
ダメじゃん
I have to do it properly.
ちゃんとやらなきゃ
I can't stop it now.
すぐに止められないよ
yes.
はい
When will you bring it now?
今はいつ持ってくる?
Tomorrow's pro wrestling?
明日のプロレス?
yes.
はい
I didn't make it in time.
間に合わなかったです
Didn't make it in time?
間に合わなかった?
No.
ダメだよ
It has to be set up properly.
ちゃんと仕掛けられなきゃ
yes.
はい
That's always the case.
いつもそれじゃん
That's when I got really horny.
すごいエッチした時だね
Have you ever been given time?
時間されたことある?
be?
ある?
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
yes.
はい
It will look like this.
こんな感じでします
It's no good if the camera shakes.
ぶれたらダメだよ、カメラ
yes.
はい
Want to take off your socks too?
靴下も脱ぎたい?
I want to take it off.
脱ぎたい
Go to work properly.
ちゃんと出勤してよ
The 20,000 yen is enough for today, so bring it tomorrow.
2万円はもう今日はいいから、明日持ってきて
See you then.
じゃあ ね